Keep an eye on Lombard as well.
To increase RBI,
look at the chart of ICC Lombard here. The top gainer in futures trading is
absolutely above 2.25%. Deepanshu, as far as ICC Lombard is
concerned, see, this stock was
clearly seen seeing April in the short term and
if you see in today's training session also,
a small side base consolidation that had happened, a
record was seen coming from it today also,
so from the immediate
perspective, I would say that the levels of 1360 are
very important for it in the short term,
as long as it is above 1360, its trade will
remain positive in the short term. At least
we cannot see the levels till 1470 of
Lombard, keep an eye on it, the movement is happening.